fleximoms.in 2013-11-29

# Fleximoms - India's only Workflex readiness specialist

**Fleximoms** is committed to protecting the privacy of users of our website. Your personal information is shared only as a part of the search process on the site. Wherever information is gathered you are made aware of the privacy practices we follow. Since Fleximoms is committed to facilitating job searches for professionals, we do need to collect, process, maintain and distribute information submitted by you for this express purpose. This information would include names and descriptions, contact details and resumes, besides other relevant information, and will be used expressly for the objectives of Fleximoms as a facilitator to candidates, companies and related stakeholders. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect in other ways. Nor does it apply to websites we are linked to and which are not owned by Fleximoms. Do review the privacy policy of these sites since we are not responsible for information submitted to or gathered by these websites. 

The Fleximoms team adheres to this Privacy Policy and understands the need for discretion in handling personal information. In case you wish to modify or delete any of your information from our database, you could do so by writing into team@fleximoms.in. Information already shared with a potential employer will still remain in their records. When a candidate applies for a job, her/his resume and details are forwarded to the potential employer. 

Emails and e-Newsletters will be sent to you by Fleximoms with updates and relevant information. You can unsubscribe to the same as indicated on these communications, if you like. 

Information from companies and organizations is requested to create an account. Employers are then requested to provide precise information about job opportunites which will be posted and be on view for candidates seeking jobs. Jobs are listed on the specific request on employers and viewed on a Fleximoms webpage and format. These may or may not include the employer’s name or contact details, as per the request of the organization. Job postings can be modified or deleted by an authorized person by sending a mail to [jobs@fleximoms.in](mailto:jobs@fleximoms.in). Company information may be modified by sending an email to [employer@fleximoms.in](mailto:employer@fleximoms.in)

Fleximoms gathers and aggregates information about users, employers and other stakeholders to either enhance the quality of service provided or assess the user groups. This is done anonymously and shared only if it is already in the public domain or with permission. 

The **Tell a Friend** link on the website will require you to enter your friend’s name and email address. The details are used to send your friend an email inviting her/him to the site. This is a third party application which is governed by its own Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. 

Fleximoms **partners** with diverse individuals and organizations to enhance services provided to users – candidates, companies and advertisers. Wherever a partner is involved, users will be advised, as third party partners are governed by their own Privacy Policy and Terms of use, and Fleximoms is not responsible for them. Users are encouraged to check out the Privacy Policies of these partners. 

A user's **personal information** may need to be shared by Fleximoms if necessary to comply with judicial, administrative or other governmental subpoenas, warrants, or where we deem necessary at our sole discretion in order to protect the safety of users of our website or members of the public. 

**Conversation Spaces:** If you use the Fleximoms blog or later additions like a chat or bulletin board on the website, you should know that any personally identifiable information you enter can be read, accessed, gathered and used by other users. Fleximoms is not responsible for information you may submit at these forums. 

**IP Addresses** are used by Fleximoms to analyse trends, track user movements and aggregate demographic data. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information 

Fleximoms uses **Cookies** to enhance the website for usage. Cookies are stored on the user’s hard drive with information that enables us to monitor your preferences and customize your account pages on the basis of your requirements. Cookies do not collect personally identifiable data – they only identify the computer you usually operate from. When you close your browser, the cookie terminates. You can delete a cookie and set your browser to not accept cookies. However, this will prevent you from using any personalized features on the site that are useful to other users. 

Cookies may be placed by third-party **advertisers** on the website in order to recognize user’s computers and gather information for targeted advertising. Fleximoms is not responsible for these advertisers and the content of their advertisements. 

While Fleximoms uses process and technology to protect user’s personal information from misuse, we cannot guarantee complete security or that third parties may get this information from other sources. A password protection function has been built in to keep your personal information secure and you may change this at any time. 

**Changes** to the Privacy Policy may be made occasionally and will reflect on this web page with the update date. In the event of a substantial change, users will be notified as well. If Fleximoms changes ownership, we may sell or transfer all information including personal user information to the new owners of the website. Users will be notified and may modify or delete their information at that stage. 

If you have any clarifications you require in connection with this Privacy Policy, or any suggestions, please first contact [team@fleximoms.in](mailto:team@fleximoms.in) and we shall be happy to respond.
